{"data":[{"question":"The earliest steam-driven vehicles produced great amount of noise.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The earliest ","b":"vehicles ","c":"produced ","d":"great ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Great-> large","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The double bull's eye in center of a dart board is worth fifty points.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"double ","b":"bull's eye ","c":"in center ","d":"is worth ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- In center-> at center","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Seaweed nurtures numerous communities of living things, which are protected under the wet coverings of the weeds while the tide out.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"numerous ","b":"which ","c":"under ","d":"tide out","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Tide out-> tide draws out","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The wankle engine, sometimes referred as a rotary engine, delivers more power for its size than a conventional piston engine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sometimes","b":"referred as ","c":"delivers ","d":"for ","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Referred as-> referred to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Farm animals have been regardless by nearly all societies as a valuable economic resource.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"regardless ","b":"nearly ","c":"as ","d":"resource","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Regardless-> regarded","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Bauxite ores differ considerably physical appearance, according to their impurities and structural compositions.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"considerably physical ","b":"according to ","c":"their ","d":"impurities ","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Considerably physical-> considerably in physical","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Helen Vendler's essays present key insight into and vital analyses the works of major british and American authors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"present ","b":"insight into ","c":"analyses the ","d":"major ","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Analyses the-> analyses of the","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The waterwheel is a mechanism designed to harness energy from a source instead than animals.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is ","b":"harness ","c":"from ","d":"instead ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Instead-> rather","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"No other beverage comes even close to rivaling coffee as the more widely drunk refreshment in the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"other ","b":"even ","c":"more widely ","d":"world","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- The more-> the most","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Mosquitos usually lay eggs on top stagnant water.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Mosquitos ","b":"usually ","c":"lay ","d":"top stagnant ","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Top stagnant-> top of stagnant","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}